{
    "id": "aee8946e148d4f779e5bd8938a742b5c",
    "title": "One Word Substitution",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Which of the following words can be used to refer to a speaker who does not use more words than necessary?",
            "description": "The adjective laconic is used to refer to people who say very little, but mean much.",
            "answers": [
                "Laconic",
                "Taciturn",
                "Inarticulate",
                "Garrulous"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "46bbc8e7a1aa49fe97ea1df63ed31d64"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which of the following words can be used to refer to a man who excessively caters to, worships and submits to the most outlandish or outrageous demands of his wife?",
            "description": "There is a difference between the words henpecked and uxorious. A henpecked husband is dominated by his wife. An uxorious husband is dominated by his neurosis, and his wife may not enjoy his uxoriousness.",
            "answers": [
                "Henpecked",
                "Uxorious",
                "Dipsomaniac"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "219ad4b7c88e4f31b3d517dad9ed72c4"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which of the following words is synonymous with alcoholism?",
            "description": "Dipsomania is the morbid compulsion to keep on drinking alcoholic beverages.",
            "answers": [
                "Dipsomania",
                "Kleptomania",
                "Pyromania"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "81820fe5aa954b738393ff1feefbdef2"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which of the following words can be used to refer to people who have delusions about their invincibility?",
            "description": "Megalomaniacs are people who have delusions about their invincibility.",
            "answers": [
                "Megalomaniac",
                "Pyromaniac",
                "Hypochondriac"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "cb3af7529a55459eaa156bfd1ff60435"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which of the following words can be used to refer to a person who fears shut-in or crowded places?",
            "description": "A claustrophobe is a person who fears being shut-in or being in crowded places.",
            "answers": [
                "Arsonist",
                "Agoraphobe",
                "Claustrophobe"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "f82cbcad32614c9f8cb735ea74d2dc66"
        },
        {
            "question": "A person who sneers at convention and tradition is a/an ……………………………",
            "description": "An iconoclast is a person who sneers at convention and tradition.",
            "answers": [
                "iconoclast",
                "agnostic",
                "atheist"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "678dcc470e20432eba40011fd1c000c9"
        },
        {
            "question": "A person who has morbid anxiety about his or her health is a /an ………………………….",
            "description": "A hypochondriac is a person who has morbid anxiety about his/her health.",
            "answers": [
                "martinet",
                "hypochondriac",
                "tyro",
                "virtuoso"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "908d55fa0fee498bb0f18726be8de820"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which of the following words is used to refer to the act of killing one’s wife?",
            "description": "Uxoricide is the act of killing one’s wife.",
            "answers": [
                "Sycophancy",
                "Patrimony",
                "Patricide",
                "Uxoricide"
            ],
            "correct": 3,
            "id": "50fd043071ee4e1b9ccefd9357eb605f"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which of the following words can be used to refer to a person who is a strict disciplinarian?",
            "description": "A martinet is a disciplinarian",
            "answers": [
                "Virago",
                "Chauvinist",
                "Martinet"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "6fd0a33b353940e7933540a8915a554f"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which of the following words can be used to refer to a person who tends to fixate obsessively over one thing?",
            "description": "A monomaniac is a person who tends to fixate obsessively over one thing.",
            "answers": [
                "Hypochondriac",
                "Agnostic",
                "Monomaniac"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "6c9d80abc2714fad8a6eca97a94f8e9c"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which of the following words can be used to refer to an accomplished musician?",
            "description": "A virtuoso is an accomplished musician and performer.",
            "answers": [
                "Dilettante",
                "Termagant",
                "Virtuoso"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "786196895f2a4374ad5e4ababea853b8"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which of the following words can be used to refer to an old man in a ruling position?",
            "description": "A patriarch is an old man in a ruling position.",
            "answers": [
                "Matriarch",
                "Termagant",
                "Patriarch"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "bd1e8022d2444f259f540cbfe0eaebef"
        }
    ]
}